A Guide to the Norman Sisisky Papers, 1982-2001
Library of Virginia
- Series VI. Speeches, 1983-2000., Extent: 14 boxes. (Box 77-90)
  - Suffolk Meals on Wheels Breakfast - 6 December 1991. (Box 84, Folder 38)
  - 50th Anniversary of Pearl Harbor - 7 December 1991. (Box 84, Folder 39)
  - Speech Index, 1992. (Box 84, Folder 40)
  - U.S. Relations with Israel - January 1992. (Box 84, Folder 41)
  - Health Care Town Meeting, Chesapeake - 14 January 1992. (Box 84, Folder 42)
  - Agribusiness Export Conference, Wakefield - 10 February 1992. (Box 84, Folder 43)
  - Petersburg High School American Studies Class - 21 February 1992. (Box 84, Folder 44)
  - Southside Area Democratic Women's Club, Petersburg - 22 February 1992. (Box 84, Folder 45)
  - Floor Debate on House Budget Resolution - 4 March 1992. (Box 84, Folder 46)
  - Chesapeake Democratic Committee - 14 March 1992. (Box 84, Folder 47)
  - White House Commemorative Coin Act - 19 March 1992. (Box 84, Folder 48)
  - Norfolk State University Community Service Banquet, Chesapeake - 20 March 1992. (Box 84, Folder 49)
  - Alrod Enterprises, Inc. - 23 March 1992. (Box 84, Folder 50)
  - Procurement Fair, Fort Lee - 23 March 1992. (Box 84, Folder 51)
  - AARP, Chapter 1399, Petersburg - 13 April 1992. (Box 85, Folder 1)
  - Naval Civilian Managers Association - 15 April 1992. (Box 85, Folder 2)
  - Phi Kappa Phi Honor Society, Richmond - 22 April 1992. (Box 85, Folder 3)
  - Colonial Heights Kiwanis Club - 22 April 1992. (Box 85, Folder 4)
  - Smithfield Kiwanis Club - 23 April 1992. (Box 85, Folder 5)
  - Prince George Heritage Fair - 25 April 1992. (Box 85, Folder 6)
  - Hampton Roads Maritime Association, Norfolk - 27 April 1992. (Box 85, Folder 7)
  - City Line Road Testimony - 28 April 1992. (Box 85, Folder 8)
  - Amelia Day Festival - 9 May 1992. (Box 85, Folder 9)
  - American Hellenic Educational Progressive Association, Hopewell - 10 May 1992. (Box 85, Folder 10)
  - National Small Business Week - 12 May 1992. (Box 85, Folder 11)
  - Naval Sea Combat Systems Engineering Station Groundbreaking, Suffolk - 18 May 1992. (Box 85, Folder 12)
  - "Impact of the American Product Liability System on Small Business" - 20 May1992. (Box 85, Folder 13)
  - Fourth Congressional District Democratic Party Convention, Prince George - 23 May 1992. (Box 85, Folder 14)
  - Portsmouth Memorial Day Parade - 25 May 1992. (Box 85, Folder 15)
  - Floor Statement on HR 5006 - 3 June 1992. (Box 85, Folder 16)
  - Air Force Association, Tidewater Chapter, Norfolk - 5 June 1992. (Box 85, Folder 17)
  - Area 2, NAACP, Norfolk State University - 6 June 1992. (Box 85, Folder 18)
  - Lakeland High School Commencement, Suffolk - 10 June 1992. (Box 85, Folder 19)
  - Lake Gaston Pipeline Project Hearing, Virginia Beach - 13 June 1992. (Box 85, Folder 20)
  - "First Citizen" Banquet Honoring Frederick H. Creekmore, Chesapeake - 19 June 1992. (Box 85, Folder 21)
  - Bennetts Creek Navigation Project Dedication, Suffolk - 22 June 1992. (Box 85, Folder 22)
  - Speech Index, 26 June - 7 September 1992. (Box 85, Folder 23)
  - Procurement Fair, Chesapeake - 26 June 1992. (Box 85, Folder 24)
  - House Ways and Means Committee, Subcommittee on Select Revenue Measures, Misclassification of Independent Contractors - 23 July 1992. (Box 85, Folder 25)
  - Chesapeake - 24 July 1992. (Box 85, Folder 26)
  - Hopewell, Petersburg, and Prince George Democratic Committees - 8 August 1992. (Box 85, Folder 27)
  - Introduction of John Marsh, Fort Lee - 8 August 1992. (Box 85, Folder 28)
  - Teacher's Workshop, Portsmouth - 15 August 1992. (Box 85, Folder 29)
  - Suffolk Democrats - 18 August 1992. (Box 85, Folder 30)
  - Project "Cares" Luncheon, Emporia - 20 August 1992. (Box 85, Folder 31)
  - Naval Civilian Managers Association, Portsmouth - 27 August 1992. (Box 85, Folder 32)
  - Hopewell Rotary Club - 1 September 1992. (Box 85, Folder 33)
  - Virginia Bankers Association, Petersburg - 1 September 1992. (Box 85, Folder 34)
  - Franklin/Southampton County Rotary Club - 4 September 1992. (Box 85, Folder 35)
  - Powhatan County - 7 September 1992. (Box 85, Folder 36)
  - Speech Index, 5 October - 11 December 1992. (Box 85, Folder 37)
  - Coal Export Tax Credit to Energy Bill - 5 October 1992. (Box 85, Folder 38)
  - Family Fun Festival, North Anna Power Station - 10 October 1992. (Box 85, Folder 39)
  - Chesapeake Men for Progress - 10 October 1992. (Box 85, Folder 40)
  - Indo-American Society Dinner, Virginia Beach - 11 October 1992. (Box 85, Folder 41)
  - National Association of Military Retirees, Colonial Heights - 15 October 1992. (Box 85, Folder 42)
  - National Association of Retired Federal Employees, Louisa County - 15 October 1992. (Box 85, Folder 43)
  - Amelia Democrats Fish Fry - 17 October 1992. (Box 85, Folder 44)
  - Ruritan Zone 5 Summer Meeting, Windsor - 21 October 1992. (Box 85, Folder 45)
  - Nottoway County Sports Complex - 23 October 1992. (Box 85, Folder 46)
  - Neighbors Place Apartment Complex, Zuni - 23 October 1992. (Box 85, Folder 47)
  - Black Civic League, Chesapeake - 24 October 1992. (Box 85, Folder 48)
  - Crater District Agency for Aging, Fort Lee - 27 October 1992. (Box 85, Folder 49)
  - Deep Creek Senior Citizens Club - 27 October 1992. (Box 85, Folder 50)
  - Business Opportunities Seminar on Trade With Canada - 6 November 1992. (Box 85, Folder 51)
  - Health Insurance Fair, Chesapeake - 7 November 1992. (Box 85, Folder 52)
  - Ship Services Support Facility, Norfolk Naval Shipyard - 11 December 1992. (Box 85, Folder 53)
  - Portsmouth Naval Hospital - 11 December 1992. (Box 85, Folder 54)
  - Speech Index, 1993. (Box 86, Folder 1)
  - Conference on Security Policy, Munich - 7 February 1993. (Box 86, Folder 2)
  - Jewish Community Alliance, Jacksonville, FL - 13 February 1993. (Box 86, Folder 3)
  - MAPI Government Procurement Conference - 4 March 1993. (Box 86, Folder 4)
  - Emergency Shelter Annual Roast, Richmond - 8 March 1993. (Box 86, Folder 5)
  - C-17 Joint Hearing - 9 March 1993. (Box 86, Folder 6)
  - C-17 Joint Hearing - 10 March 1993. (Box 86, Folder 7)
  - Portsmouth Democratic Committee - 20 March 1993. (Box 86, Folder 8)
  - DOD Procurement Conference, Williamsburg - 14 April 1993. (Box 86, Folder 9)
  - Fourth District Nominating Convention, Prince George - 17 April 1993. (Box 86, Folder 10)
  - BRAC Testimony Navair Deport, Norfolk - 20 April 1993. (Box 86, Folder 11)
  - BRAC Testimony Naval Undersea Warfare Center - 20 April 1993. (Box 86, Folder 12)
  - Fort Lee Activity Day - 24 April 1993. (Box 86, Folder 13)
  - House Appropriations Committee, Subcommittee on Transportation - 6 May 1993. (Box 86, Folder 14)
  - 13th Annual Small Business Contracting Day - 14 May 1993. (Box 86, Folder 15)
  - Phillips Volunteer Fire Station Open House, Chesterfield - 15 May 1993. (Box 86, Folder 16)
  - Memorial Day Parade, Portsmouth - 31 May 1993. (Box 86, Folder 17)
  - Virginia Forum Luncheon, Washington, D.C. - 8 June 1993. (Box 86, Folder 18)
  - BRAC Hearings - 16 June 1993. (Box 86, Folder 19)
  - BRAC Regional Hearings, Norfolk - 11 June 1993. (Box 86, Folder 20)
  - Civic League and South Norfolk Ruritan Club - 4 July 1993. (Box 86, Folder 21)
  - Blue Chip Enterprise Intitiative Awards Ceremony - 7 July 1993. (Box 86, Folder 22)
  - Naval Undersea Warfare Center, Suffolk - 12 July 1993. (Box 86, Folder 23)
  - House Small Business Committee, Regulatory Flexibility Act - 28 July 1993. (Box 86, Folder 24)
  - House Government Operations Committee, Subcommittee on Commerce, Consumer and Monetary Affairs - 8 June 1993. (Box 86, Folder 25)
  - Fort Lee Celebration, NCO Club - 19 August 1993. (Box 86, Folder 26)
  - Black Caucus Virginia Day - 14 September 1993. (Box 86, Folder 27)
  - 150th Anniversary of B'nai B'rith, Arnold Gamey Lodge #1195, Norfolk - 15 October 1993. (Box 86, Folder 28)
  - "Homerama," Tidewater Builders Association, Chesapeake - 15 October 1993. (Box 86, Folder 29)
  - Quartermaster Regimental Ball, Fort Lee - 22 October 1993. (Box 86, Folder 30)
  - House Small Business Committee, Paperwork Reduction Act - 28 October 1993. (Box 86, Folder 31)
  - Paperwork Reduction Act Hearing - 28 October 1993. (Box 86, Folder 32)
  - Federal Retirees Health Insurance Fair, Virginia Beach - 30 October 1993. (Box 86, Folder 33)
  - National Soft Drink Association Luncheon - 4 November 1993. (Box 86, Folder 34)
  - Navy Supply Corps Association - 10 November 1993. (Box 86, Folder 35)
  - New Grade Crossing Barrier for High-Speed Rail - 16 November 1993. (Box 86, Folder 36)
  - North Atlantic Assembly, Defense and Security Committee - 17 November 1993. (Box 86, Folder 37)
  - Surface Navy Association - 23 November 1993. (Box 86, Folder 38)
  - Consolidated Launcher Technology, Chesapeake - 16 December 1993. (Box 86, Folder 39)
  - Congressional Agenda for Change in Industrial Policy and Acquisition Planning (1993). (Box 86, Folder 40)
  - Speech Index, 1994. (Box 87, Folder 1)
  - Prince George County Heritage Fair - 30 April 1994. (Box 87, Folder 2)
  - Goochland Democrats - 9 December 1994. (Box 87, Folder 3)
  - Boykins/Branchville/Mewsoms Regional Water and Sewer System Groundbreaking - 8 December 1994. (Box 87, Folder 4)
  - Urban Summit, Richmond - 8 December 1994. (Box 87, Folder 5)
  - Election Victory Statement - 8 November 1994. (Box 87, Folder 6)
  - Bachelor Enlisted Quarters, Norfolk Naval Shipyard - January 1994. (Box 87, Folder 7)
  - Concord Coalition, South Hampton Roads Chapter - 28 October 1994. (Box 87, Folder 8)
  - Amelia County Elementary School Dedication - 23 October 1994. (Box 87, Folder 9)
  - Southside Democratic Women, Petersburg - 22 October 1994. (Box 87, Folder 10)
  - National Association of Military Retirees, Colonial Heights - 30 April 1994. (Box 87, Folder 11)
  - Rotary Club Luncheon, Chesapeake - 19 October 1994. (Box 87, Folder 12)
  - Eden Pines Ribbon Cutting - 16 October 1994. (Box 87, Folder 13)
  - Portsmouth Chamber of Commerce, Military Affairs Committee - 12 October 1994. (Box 87, Folder 14)
  - Chesapeake Care Clinic - 2 October 1994. (Box 87, Folder 15)
  - Chesapeake Forward - 18 September 1994. (Box 87, Folder 16)
  - Hickory Ruritan Club - 2 September 1994. (Box 87, Folder 17)
  - Northup-Grumman Dedication, Chesapeake - 1 September 1994. (Box 87, Folder 18)
  - Rotary Club Luncheon, Chesapeake - 31 August 1994. (Box 87, Folder 19)
  - Portsmouth Rotary Club - 7 July 1994. (Box 87, Folder 20)
  - Emporia Rotary Club - 5 July 1994. (Box 87, Folder 21)
  - Investiture of City Officials, Suffolk - 1 July 1994. (Box 87, Folder 22)
  - National League of Cities, Transportation and Communications Committee - 18 June 1994. (Box 87, Folder 23)
  - Price Waterhouse Breakfast - 17 May 1994. (Box 87, Folder 24)
  - Funding for CVN-76 Carrier - 18 May 1994. (Box 87, Folder 25)
  - Blackhawk Shootdown Over Iraq - 14 April 1994. (Box 87, Folder 26)
  - Pioneer Unmanned Aerial Vehicle Program - 24 March 1994. (Box 87, Folder 27)
  - International Council of Shopping Centers, Pentagon City - 22 March 1994. (Box 87, Folder 28)
  - Anti-Excise Tax on Tobacco Rally - 9 March 1994. (Box 87, Folder 29)
  - Department of Defense Smoking Ban - March 1994. (Box 87, Folder 30)
  - Portsmouth Naval Hospital, Acute Care Facility Groundbreaking - 28 February 1994. (Box 87, Folder 31)
  - Democratic Party Workers - 13 February 1994. (Box 87, Folder 32)
  - House Committee on Energy and Commerce, Subcommittee on Commerce, Consumer Protection, and Competitiveness - 2 February 1994. (Box 87, Folder 33)
  - Portsmouth Kiwanis Club - 19 January 1994. (Box 87, Folder 34)
  - Environmental Technology Center, Portsmouth - 11 January 1994. (Box 87, Folder 35)
  - Utility and Heavy Contractors, Chesapeake - 5 January 1994. (Box 87, Folder 36)
  - Speech Directory, 1995. (Box 88, Folder 1)
  - Judiciary Committee, Subcommittee on Commercial and Administrative Law - 3 January 1995. (Box 88, Folder 2)
  - Paperwork Reduction Act - 7 February 1995. (Box 88, Folder 3)
  - Government Reform and Oversight Committee, Subcommittee on National Economic Growth, Natural Resources, and Regulatory Affairs - 7 February 1995. (Box 88, Folder 4)
  - Support of H.R. 830 - 22 February 1995. (Box 88, Folder 5)
  - Support of H.R. 926 - 28 February 1995. (Box 88, Folder 6)
  - Transportation Committee, Subcommittee on Surface Transportation - 8 March 1995. (Box 88, Folder 7)
  - Appropriations Committee, Subcommittee on Transportation - 21 March 1995. (Box 88, Folder 8)
  - McCain Report on Military Capabilities and Readiness - 22 March 1995. (Box 88, Folder 9)
  - Kenner Army Hospital - 5 April 1995. (Box 88, Folder 10)
  - National Weather Service Wakefield Office Dedication - 19 April 1995. (Box 88, Folder 11)
  - Lil Hart Campaign Kick-off - 19 April 1995. (Box 88, Folder 12)
  - EDO Ribbon-Cutting Ceremony, Chesapeake - 20 April 1995. (Box 88, Folder 13)
  - Suffolk Education Association Dinner - 20 April 1995. (Box 88, Folder 14)
  - Prince George County Heritage Fair - 21 April 1995. (Box 88, Folder 15)
  - BRAC Hearing, Recommendation to Close Fort Pickett - 4 May 1995. (Box 88, Folder 16)
  - BRAC Hearing, Recommendation to Realign Kenner Hospital - 4 May 1995. (Box 88, Folder 17)
  - Thirty Group Speech - 9 May 1995. (Box 88, Folder 18)
  - Hopewell, Prince George and Petersburg Democratic Party - 13 May 1995. (Box 88, Folder 19)
  - New Tractor Plant Unveiling, Chesapeake - 19 May 1995. (Box 88, Folder 20)
  - Armed Forces Day, Norfolk Naval Shipyard - 20 May 1995. (Box 88, Folder 21)
  - Sisisky Birthday Roast - 10 June 1995. (Box 88, Folder 22)
  - Shays Amendment, H.R. 1976 - 18 July 1995. (Box 88, Folder 23)
  - Bosnia Self-Defense Act, S. 21 - 1 August 1995. (Box 88, Folder 24)
  - Senate Agriculture Committee - 17 August 1995. (Box 88, Folder 25)
  - Federal Managers Association, Norfolk - 19 August 1995. (Box 88, Folder 26)
  - Senate Agriculture Committee - 22 August 1995. (Box 88, Folder 27)
  - Army Corps of Engineers, Norfolk - 25 August 1995. (Box 88, Folder 28)
  - Southampton Middle School Dedication - 27 August 1995. (Box 88, Folder 29)
  - Chesapeake Rotary Club - 28 August 1995. (Box 88, Folder 30)
  - Bosnia Statement - 17 November 1995. (Box 88, Folder 31)
  - Arrival of Pacific Escort, Norfolk Naval Shipyard - 27 November 1995. (Box 88, Folder 32)
  - Great Bridge High School, Chesapeake - 1 December 1995. (Box 88, Folder 33)
  - Chamber of Commerce Luncheon, Chesapeake - 1 Deecember 1995. (Box 88, Folder 34)
  - Oscar Smith High School, Chesapeake - 1 December 1995. (Box 88, Folder 35)
  - Speech Directory, 1996. (Box 88, Folder 36)
  - Blue Dog Press Conference - 4 January 1996. (Box 88, Folder 37)
  - Municipal Solide Waste Flow Control - 30 January 1996. (Box 88, Folder 38)
  - Joint Training, Analysis and Simulation Center, Suffolk - January 1996. (Box 88, Folder 39)
  - Farm Bill (1996). (Box 88, Folder 40)
  - Shays Amendment, H.R. 2854 - 29 February 1996. (Box 88, Folder 41)
  - Talking Points for Interview - 29 February 1996. (Box 88, Folder 42)
  - Appropriations Committee, Subcommittee on Energy and Water - 5 March 1996. (Box 88, Folder 43)
  - Elizabeth River Project - 10 March 1996. (Box 88, Folder 44)
  - Hampton Roads Military Diplomats, Norfolk Naval Shipyard - 25 March 1996. (Box 88, Folder 45)
  - Privatization Conference, Norfolk - 26 March 1996. (Box 88, Folder 46)
  - Hot Rod Jamboreem Chesapeake - 10 April 1996. (Box 88, Folder 47)
  - Prince George Heritage Fair - 27 April 1996. (Box 88, Folder 48)
  - American Legion Auxiliary Unit 284 Tribute - 7 June 1996. (Box 88, Folder 49)
  - Jim McNeer Ceremonies, Petersburg - 9 June 1996. (Box 88, Folder 50)
  - Durbin Amendment H.R. 3630 Opposition - 12 June 1996. (Box 88, Folder 51)
  - Hobson Amendment H.R. 3630 Opposition - 12 June 1996. (Box 88, Folder 52)
  - Procurement Conference - 24 June 1996. (Box 88, Folder 53)
  - Installation of New Chesapeake Officers - 28 June 1996. (Box 88, Folder 54)
  - Business and Industry Appreciation Dinner - 20 September 1996. (Box 88, Folder 55)
  - Virginia Black Caucus Legislative Conference, St. Paul's College, Lawrenceville - 12 October 1996. (Box 88, Folder 56)
  - Jefferson Awards Luncheon - 14 October 1996. (Box 88, Folder 57)
  - Hampton Clinic Dedication - 15 October 1996. (Box 88, Folder 58)
  - Colonial Heights Military Retirees - 17 October 1996. (Box 88, Folder 59)
  - Norfolk Retired Federal Employees Health Care Fair - 9 November 1996. (Box 88, Folder 60)
  - ODU Modeling and Simulation Center - 6 December 1996. (Box 88, Folder 61)
  - Speech Index, 1997-1998. (Box 89, Folder 1)
  - Tecnico Plant Dedication - 17 January 1997. (Box 89, Folder 2)
  - Portsmouth Rotary - 30 January 1997. (Box 89, Folder 3)
  - Virginia Fine Arts Leadership Conference, Williamsburg (Jan Faircloth) - 6 March 1997. (Box 89, Folder 4)
  - House Ways and Means Committee, Subcommittee on Health - 13 March 1997. (Box 89, Folder 5)
  - House Appropriations Committee, Subcommittee on Energy and Water Development - 28 March 1997. (Box 89, Folder 6)
  - Harrison Villa Groundbreaking, Fort Lee - 14 April 1997. (Box 89, Folder 7)
  - Fourth District Delegates to the 1997 Democratic Convention, Petersburg - 19 April 1997. (Box 89, Folder 8)
  - Prince George County Heritage Fair - 26 April 1997. (Box 89, Folder 9)
  - Chesapeake Consumer Housing Fair - 3 May 1997. (Box 89, Folder 10)
  - Air Force Association Salute to Small Business, Herndon - 6 May 1997. (Box 89, Folder 11)
  - Old Dominion University Commencement - 10 May 1997. (Box 89, Folder 12)
  - International Federation of Professional and Technical Engineers - 29 May 1997. (Box 89, Folder 13)
  - VSU Consumer Housing Fair - 7 June 1997. (Box 89, Folder 14)
  - Remarks on H.R. 2015 - 25 June 1997. (Box 89, Folder 15)
  - Opposition to Lowey Amendment to H.R. 2160 - 24 July 1997. (Box 89, Folder 16)
  - Neumann-Kanjorski Amendment to H.R. 2160 - 24 July 1997. (Box 89, Folder 17)
  - Colorectal Cancer Screening Provisions of H.R. 2015 - 30 July 1997. (Box 89, Folder 18)
  - 12th Annual Crop Field Day, VSU - 26 August 1997. (Box 89, Folder 19)
  - Peanut Growers Cooperative Marketing Association - 27 August 1997. (Box 89, Folder 20)
  - Petersburg Federal Correctional Institution - 19 September 1997. (Box 89, Folder 21)
  - Dr. James McNeer Inauguration, Richard Bland College - 3 October 1997. (Box 89, Folder 22)
  - SBA Loan Programs in Lower Income Communities - 22 October 1997. (Box 89, Folder 23)
  - Small Business Reauthorization Act, S. 1139 - 8 November 1997. (Box 89, Folder 24)
  - Fort Pickett Welcome and Open House - 4 December 1997. (Box 89, Folder 25)
  - Fort Pickett Welcome and Open House - 4 December 1997. (Box 89, Folder 25)
  - Soldier-One-Stop Center Opening, Fort Lee - 5 December 1997. (Box 89, Folder 26)
  - Norfolk Naval Shipyard, Portsmouth Association - 11 December 1997. (Box 89, Folder 27)
  - Harrison Villa Opening, Fort Lee - 26 January 1998. (Box 89, Folder 28)
  - Southside Area Democratic Women's Club - 28 February 1998. (Box 89, Folder 29)
  - CNO's Executive Panel Breakfast - 24 March 1998. (Box 89, Folder 30)
  - House Appropriations Committee, Subcommittee on Energy and Water Development - 27 March 1998. (Box 89, Folder 31)
  - Prince George Heritage Fair - 25 April 1998. (Box 89, Folder 32)
  - Virginia National Guard Convention, Richmond - 25 April 1998. (Box 89, Folder 33)
  - Sidney M. Oman Cancer Treatment Center, Chesapeake - 26 April 1998. (Box 89, Folder 34)
  - Speech Index, 1998-1999. (Box 89, Folder 35)
  - Congressman Robert C. "Bobby" Scott, Chesapeake Democratic Committee, American Values Award Dinner - 16 May 1998. (Box 89, Folder 36)
  - Hampton Roads Chamber of Commerce, Chesapeake - 8 June 1998. (Box 89, Folder 37)
  - Southside Area Chapter of the American Red Cross, Petersburg - 30 June 1998. (Box 89, Folder 38)
  - Norfolk Central Labor Council - 1 July 1998. (Box 89, Folder 39)
  - Southside Regional Fire Academy - 9 July 1998. (Box 89, Folder 40)
  - Death of Former Rep. Wat Abitt - 14 July 1998. (Box 89, Folder 41)
  - Deaths of Capitol Police Officers - 27 July 1998. (Box 89, Folder 42)
  - Naval Civilian Managers Association, Portsmouth - 13 August 1998. (Box 89, Folder 43)
  - AFL-CIO Convention, Williamsburg - 14 August 1998. (Box 89, Folder 44)
  - Petersburg Democratic Committee - 10 October 1998. (Box 89, Folder 45)
  - Chesapeake Habitat Interfaith Partners - 11 October 1998. (Box 89, Folder 46)
  - JTASC, Suffolk - 21 October 1998. (Box 89, Folder 47)
  - Sid Oman Interview/WHRO Taping - 21-22 October 1998. (Box 89, Folder 48)
  - Poplar Springs Hospital, Petersburg - 28 October 1998. (Box 89, Folder 49)
  - NNSY, Portsmouth Association - 10 December 1998. (Box 89, Folder 50)
  - CNN Interview - 13 December 1998. (Box 89, Folder 51)
  - Remarks About Israel and Iraq (1999). (Box 90, Folder 1)
  - Community Man of the Year Award, Portsmouth - 10 January 1999. (Box 90, Folder 2)
  - Southside Area Democratic Women and Associates - 27 February 1999. (Box 90, Folder 3)
  - Sid Oman Interview - 5 April 1999. (Box 90, Folder 4)
  - Suffolk Rotary Club - 8 April 1999. (Box 90, Folder 5)
  - WAC Museum Groundbreaking, Fort Lee - 9 April 1999. (Box 90, Folder 6)
  - Prince George Heritage Fair - 24 April 1999. (Box 90, Folder 7)
  - Charette Health Care Center, Portsmouth Naval Hospital - 30 April 1999. (Box 90, Folder 8)
  - VFW Loyalty Day Parade, Colonial Heights - 1 May 1999. (Box 90, Folder 9)
  - Petersburg Relay for Life, Richard Bland College - 21 May 1999. (Box 90, Folder 10)
  - Chesterfield Consumer Housing Fair, VSU - 22 May 1999. (Box 90, Folder 11)
  - Sid Oman Interview - 1 June 1999. (Box 90, Folder 12)
  - Southside Area Democratic Women - 4 June 1999. (Box 90, Folder 13)
  - Water 2000 Project, Amelia - 9 July 1999. (Box 90, Folder 14)
  - Route 168/South Battlefield Boulevard Groundbreaking - 12 July 1999. (Box 90, Folder 15)
  - Harrison Villa II Groundbreaking, Fort Lee - 8 September 1999. (Box 90, Folder 16)
  - Helen Person Tribute, Third Baptist Church, Portsmouth - 19 September 1999. (Box 90, Folder 17)
  - Norfolk Dredging Company 100th Anniversary, Chesapeake - 25 September 1999. (Box 90, Folder 18)
  - Ministers' Meeting with Rep. Scott, Portsmouth - 25 September 1999. (Box 90, Folder 19)
  - Tricare Clinic Ribbon Cutting, Chesapeake - 27 September 1999. (Box 90, Folder 20)
  - Retired Officers Association, Fort Lee - 8 October 1999. (Box 90, Folder 21)
  - Beth Sholom Gardens Groundbreaking, Richmond - 10 October 1999. (Box 90, Folder 22)
  - Stakeholder Coordination Meeting for Craney Island - 22 November 1999. (Box 90, Folder 23)
  - Boat Ride on the Elizabeth River, Great Bridge Lock to Craney Island - 22 November 1999. (Box 90, Folder 24)
  - Intercoastal Waterway Bridge Signing Ceremony, Great Bridge - 22 November 1999. (Box 90, Folder 25)
  - Chesapeake Local Census Office - 7 December 1999. (Box 90, Folder 26)
  - John F. Kennedy Middle School Honoring Franklin Chatman - 10 December 1999. (Box 90, Folder 27)
  - Sid Oman Show - 11 February 2000. (Box 90, Folder 28)
  - Franklin Agricultural Agency - 12 February 2000. (Box 90, Folder 29)
  - Appomattox Regional Governor's School, Petersburg - 17 March 2000. (Box 90, Folder 30)
  - Savings Bond Campaign Kickoff, Norfolk - 31 March 2000. (Box 90, Folder 31)
  - NNSY, Portsmouth Association - 31 March 2000. (Box 90, Folder 32)
  - Friends of the Portsmouth Naval Shipyard Museum - 15 May 2000. (Box 90, Folder 33)
  - Petersburg Relay for Life - 2 June 2000. (Box 90, Folder 34)
  - Great Bridge Jaycees Award Honoring Lil Hart, Chesapeake - 1 June 2000. (Box 90, Folder 35)
  - Habitat for Humanity, Chesapeake - 16 September 2000. (Box 90, Folder 36)
  - Beth Sholom Gardens Dedication - 3 December 2000. (Box 90, Folder 37)